Guide to the Susan H. Douglas political Americana collection, [1783?]-1961.
Douglas, Susan H. Political Americana Collection, [1783?]-1961
- Series II. Bric-a-Brac
  - "Lincoln's Home, Springfield, Illinois" Wooden Plate, 2214.BB0126 (Box 72)
  - McKinley "Our Next President" Metal Portrait Ash Tray, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0127 (Box 42)
  - "McKinley and Hobart Gold Standard" Ink Well, 1896; 2214.BB0128 (Box 34)
  - Presidential Portrait Tray, ca. 1897; 2214.BB0129 (Box 42)
  - McKinley Cast Iron Portrait Plaque, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0130 (Box 38)
  - McKinley Commemorative Metal Bust, 1908; 2214.BB0131 (Box 34)
  - McKinley "Continental" Portrait Paperweight, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0132 (Box 31)
  - McKinley-Temple of Music Memorial Paperweight, ca. 1901; 2214.BB0133 (Box 31)
  - "President McKinley" Portrait Paper Weight, ca. 1897-1901; 2214.BB0134 (Box 31)
  - "Wm. McKinley" Portrait Glass Paperweight, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0135 (Box 31)
  - McKinley Ceramic Portrait Tile, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0136 (Box 17)
  - McKinley Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0137 (Box 10)
  - McKinley Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0138 (Box 10)
  - McKinley Ceramic Portait Pitcher, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0139 (Box 2)
  - McKinley and Spanish-American War Leaders Portrait Fan, ca. 1898; 2214.BB0140 (Box 75)
  - McKinley Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0141 (Box 10)
  - McKinley Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1901; 2214.BB0142 (Box 10)
  - McKinley Parian Portrait Bust, 2214.BB0143 (Box 15)
  - McKinley Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0144 (Box 10)
  - McKinley Ceramic Portrait Tray, 1896; 2214.BB0145 (Box 9)
  - McKinley Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0146 (Box 8)
  - McKinley-Hobart Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0147 (Box 9)
  - "McKinley" Painted Portrait Bust, 2214.BB0148 (Box 16)
  - McKinley "Protection And Prosperity" Portrait Glass Mug with Lid, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0149 (Box 22)
  - McKinley "Protection and Plenty" Glass Portrait Plate, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0150 (Box 28)
  - McKinley "Protection And Plenty" Portrait Drinking Glass, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0151 (Box 21)
  - "My Papa Will Vote for McKinley" Baby Figurine Soap and Box, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0152 (Box 147)
  - McKinley "Protection" Tin Portrait Plaque, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0153 (Box 45)
  - McKinley "It Is Gods Way" Glass Portrait Platter, ca. 1901; 2214.BB0154 (Box 29)
  - McKinley-Theodore Roosevelt "Our Candidates" Glass Flask, ca. 1900; 2214.BB0155 (Box 22)
  - "McKinley & Roosevelt" Milk Glass Portrait Plate, ca. 1900; 2214.BB0156 (Box 9)
  - Hobart "Protection, Sound Money, Prosperity" Revolving Fan, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0157 (Box 137)
  - 16 To 1: Uncle Sam's Puzzle for Old and Young, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0158 (Box 144)
  - The Cleveland Second Term Puzzle, ca. 1888-1892; 2214.BB0159 (Box 144)
  - "To The Memory of American Tin" Plate, 1892; 2214.BB0160 (Box 47)
  - Benjamin Harrison "The Nation's Pride" Portrait Fan, ca. 1888; 2214.BB0161 (Box TBD)
  - Mix and Match Portrait Cards, 1881; 2214.BB0162 (Box 146)
  - Grant Memorial Medallions and Case, ca. 1885; 2214.BB0163 (Box 71)
  - McKinley Portrait Glass Paperweight, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0164 (Box 31)
  - McKinley-Temple of Music Memorial Ashtray, ca. 1901; 2214.BB0165 (Box 42)
  - McKinley "We Mourn Our Loss" Memorial Metal Ashtray, ca. 1901; 2214.BB0166 (Box 42)
  - McKinley "1843-1901" Bronze Memorial Plaque, 2214.BB0167 (Box 46)
  - McKinley "It Is God's Way" Oval Cast Iron Memorial Platter, ca. 1901; 2214.BB0168 (Box 44)
  - McKinley-Theodore Roosevelt "Prosperity" Metal Elephant Coin Bank, ca. 1900; 2214.BB0169 (Box 34)
  - McKinley Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0170 (Box 9)
  - Bryan Portrait Metal Tray, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0171 (Box 43)
  - McKinley-Theodore Roosevelt "Integrity, Inspiration, Industry" Portrait Drinking Glass, ca. 1900; 2214.BB0172 (Box 20)
  - McKinley "Protection, Peace, Prosperity" Portrait Drinking Glass, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0173 (Box 20)
  - McKinley Portrait Drinking Glass, ca. 1900; 2214.BB0174 (Box 20)
  - McKinley Cast Iron Standing Portrait Plaque, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0175 (Box 37)
  - McKinley "It is God's Way / Lead, Kindly Light" Portrait Plaque, ca. 1901; 2214.BB0176 (Box 45)
  - McKinley Memorial Day Portrait Plaque, ca. 1901-1910; 2214.BB0177 (Box 138)
  - New York State Demonstration Voting Machine, ca. 1900; 2214.BB0178 (Box 57)
  - Garfield-Arthur-Hancock-English Snuff Box, ca. 1880; 2214.BB0179 (Box 64)
  - McKinley "Sound Money" Cardboard Badge, 1896; 2214.BB0181 (Box 196)
  - Truman Portrait Head Bottle Stopper, ca. 1948; 2214.BB0182 (Box 76)
  - Eisenhower Portrait Head Bottle Stopper, ca. 1948; 2214.BB0183 (Box 76)
  - Plaster "Alamo Entrance" Shrine with Polk-Dallas Campaign Ribbon, ca. 1844; 2214.BB0184 (Box 70)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Portrait Creamer, ca. 1933; 2214.BB0185 (Box 2)
  - "F.D. Roosevelt" Plaster Portrait Bust, 2214.BB0186 (Box 15)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt "The New Deal" Portrait Mug, ca. 1932; 2214.BB0187 (Box 3)
  - "Franklin D. Roosevelt" Ceramic Portrait Bust, ca. 1930-1945; 2214.BB0188 (Box 15)
  - "F.D. Roosevelt" Plaster Portrait Bust, 2214.BB0189 (Box 16)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt "Remember Pearl Harbor" Plaster Portrait Bust, ca. 1941-1945; 2214.BB0190 (Box 16)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Metal Bust, ca. 1951; 2214.BB0192 (Box 34)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt "Keep Roosevelt in the White House" Metal Tray, ca. 1936; 2214.BB0193 (Box 42)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt "New Deal" Portrait Coin Bank, ca. 1932; 2214.BB0194 (Box 64)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Wooden Portrait Smoking Pipe, 2214.BB0195 (Box 77)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Ceramic Portrait Head Mug, ca. 1932; 2214.BB0196 (Box 2)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Portrait Creamer, ca. 1932-1944; 2214.BB0197 (Box 3)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Portrait Bottle Stopper, ca. 1948; 2214.BB0198 (Box 76)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt "Pre-Election Celebration" Metal Admission Ticket, 1932; 2214.BB0199 (Box 200)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Drinking Glass, ca. 1936; 2214.BB0200 (Box 21)
  - "Home of President Franklin D. Roosevelt" Portrait Mug, ca. 1945-1960; 2214.BB0201 (Box 3)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt "At The Wheel For A New Deal" Portrait Clock, ca. 1932; 2214.BB0202 (Box 51)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt "The Man of the Hour" Portrait Clock, ca. 1933; 2214.BB0203 (Box 35)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Glass Portrait Paperweight, ca. 1904; 2214.BB0204 (Box 31)
  - Theodore Roosevelt "1912 / Teddy" Plaster Caricature Bust, 2214.BB0205 (Box 16)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Portrait Plate, ca. 1901; 2214.BB0207 (Box 8)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Ceramic Portrait Tile, 1916; 2214.BB0208 (Box 17)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Commemorative Metal Bust, 1921; 2214.BB0210 (Box 34)
  - Theodore Roosevelt-Prince Henry Pewter Cup, ca. 1902; 2214.BB0211 (Box 64)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Rough Rider Portrait Tray, ca. 1898; 2214.BB0212 (Box 43)
  - "President Roosevelt 1902 Oyster Bay" Glass Punch Cup, ca. 1902; 2214.BB0213 (Box 21)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Metal Portrait Clock Frame, ca. 1900-1904; 2214.BB0214 (Box 39)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Standing Cutout Portrait, 1898; 2214.BB0215 (Box 138)
  - Theodore Roosevelt "A Square Deal" Glass Portrait Platter, ca. 1904; 2214.BB0216 (Box 29)
  - Theodore Roosevelt "Aggressive Fighting For the Right ..." Bronze Portrait Plaque, 1920; 2214.BB0217 (Box 46)
  - Theodore Roosevelt "Teddy And The Bear" Caricature Ceramic Vase, ca. 1904; 2214.BB0218 (Box 64)
  - "Taft For President 1952" Ceramic Mug, 2214.BB0219 (Box 3)
  - William H. Taft-Sherman "The Morning After" Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1908; 2214.BB0221 (Box 13)
  - William H. Taft Toby-Style Portrait Pitcher, ca. 1908; 2214.BB0222 (Box 2)
  - William H. Taft "1912 / Bill-A-Gain" Plaster Caricature Bust, 2214.BB0223 (Box 16)
  - William H. Taft-Sherman Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1908; 2214.BB0224 (Box 13)
  - William H. Taft Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1908; 2214.BB0225 (Box 13)
  - William H. Taft "Our Choice 1908" Ceramic Portrait Plate, 2214.BB0226 (Box 13)
  - William H. Taft / Helen Herron Taft Silver-plated Portrait Scissors, ca. 1908; 2214.BB0227 (Box 45)
  - William H. Taft-Sherman Tin "Grand Old Party Standard Bearers" Portrait Plate, 1908; 2214.BB0228 (Box 47)
  - "Garner in 1940" Miniature White Felt Hat, 2214.BB0229 (Box 76)
  - William O. Douglas Portrait Paper Fan, ca. 1948; 2214.BB0230 (Box 138)
  - Dewey Paper Fan, ca. 1948; 2214.BB0231 (Box 138)
  - Republican Elephant Metal Coin Bank, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0232 (Box 34)
  - Eisenhower Portrait Cigarette lighter, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0233 (Box 227)
  - Eisenhower Inaugural Souvenir Liquor Bottle, 1953; 2214.BB0234 (Box 22)
  - Taylor "Forget Me Not" Portrait Snuff Box, ca. 1850; 2214.BB0235 (Box 178)
  - Taylor Portrait Hand Mirror, ca. 1844; 2214.BB0236 (Box 178)
  - Taylor Portrait Hand Mirror, ca. 1848; 2214.BB0237 (Box 178)
  - Taylor-Fillmore Portrait Medallion, ca. 1848; 2214.BB0238 (Box 178)
  - Truman Monkey Coin Bank, ca. 1948; 2214.BB0239 (Box 34)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.BB0240 (Box -)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.BB0241 (Box -)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.BB0242 (Box -)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.BB0243 (Box -)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.BB0244 (Box -)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.BB0245 (Box -)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.BB0246 (Box -)
  - Uncut Sheet of Metal Willkie-Franklin D. Roosevelt Lapel Buttons, ca. 1940; 2214.BB0247 (Box 41)
  - "We Want Willkie" Compact, ca. 1940; 2214.BB0248 (Box 74)
  - "Win With Willkie" Plaster Elephant Statuette, ca. 1940; 2214.BB0249 (Box 64)
  - Willkie "Preparedness-Peace-Prosperity" Ash Tray, ca. 1940; 2214.BB0250 (Box 67)
  - Wilson Ceramic Portrait Tile, 1916; 2214.BB0251 (Box 17)
  - Wilson Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1912; 2214.BB0252 (Box 5)
  - Wilson Plaster Portrait Bust, 2214.BB0253 (Box 16)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Enameled Compact, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0254 (Box 74)
  - "Victory To Jackson" Portrait Sewing Box, ca. 1828-1832; 2214.BB0255 (Box 71)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson "Our Choice" Glass Bottle, ca. 1892-1893; 2214.BB0257 (Box 22)
  - Taylor-Washington Portrait Glass Bottle, ca. 1848; 2214.BB0258 (Box 22)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Morton Three-sided Standing Ribbon, 1888; 2214.BB0259 (Box 75)
  - Coolidge Large Standing Portrait Button, ca. 1924; 2214.BB0260 (Box 68)
  - Hoover-Curtis Rolled Inaugural Edition of the Washington Times, 1929; 2214.BB0261 (Box 165)
  - Willkie "Our Next President" Large Standing Portrait Button, ca. 1940; 2214.BB0262 (Box 68)
  - Dewey-Warren / Woods-Poage Paper Shopping Bag, ca. 1948; 2214.BB0263 (Box 87)
  - Eisenhower Green Plastic "Ike" Ring, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0264 (Box 74)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Playing Cards with Case, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0266 (Box 71)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Large Standing Portrait Button, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0267 (Box 68)
  - Eisenhower "Ike" Earrings, Bracelet, and Jewelry Stand, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0268 (Box 76)
  - Eisenhower "Ike From Abliene" Phonograph Record, 1952; 2214.BB0269 (Box 141)
  - Carton of Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Cigarettes, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0270 (Box 227)
  - Eisenhower "Clean Up With Ike" Portrait Soap, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0271 (Box 147)
  - Carton of "Stevenson for President" Cigarettes, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0272 (Box 227)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt "Happy Days Are Here Again" Caricature Portrait Mug, ca. 1932-1944; 2214.BB0273 (Box 3)
  - Case of Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Cans, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0274 (Box 33)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Can, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0274a (Box 64)
  - Grant "Let Us Have Peace" Portrait Drinking Glass, 2214.BB0275 (Box 21)
  - Wilson-William H. Taft-Theodore Roosevelt Spiegel Motion Slide, ca. 1912; 2214.BB0276 (Box 72)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Cast Iron Portrait Door Stop, ca. 1900-1904; 2214.BB0277 (Box 36)
  - William Henry Harrison Tortoise Shell Hair Comb, ca. 1841; 2214.BB0278 (Box 72)
  - Lincoln Ceramic Portrait Tile, 2214.BB0279 (Box 17)
  - Henry Clay Miniature Silhouette Portrait, 2214.BB0280 (Box 75)
  - Cleveland-Stevenson Metal Change Carrier, 1892; 2214.BB0281 (Box 74)
  - Cleveland Miniature Democratic Rooster Seal with Case, ca. 1892; 2214.BB0282 (Box 71)
  - "Harrison For Governor" Thimble, 2214.BB0283 (Box 160)
  - William H. Taft Ohio Society of New York Letter Opener, 1908; 2214.BB0285 (Box 45)
  - Hoover License Plate Ornament, ca. 1928; 2214.BB0287 (Box 41)
  - Donkey & Elephant "Super Magnetic Battling Pals" Figurines with Box, ca. 1928; 2214.BB0288 (Box 74)
  - "Hoover for President 1932" Pencil with Portrait Head Eraser, 2214.BB0289 (Box 160)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt License Plate, ca. 1944; 2214.BB0290 (Box 41)
  - Willkie Portrait License Plate Ornament, ca. 1940; 2214.BB0291 (Box 41)
  - "Willkie For President" Metal License Plate Ornament, ca. 1940; 2214.BB0292 (Box 41)
  - "For President: Thomas E. Dewey" Portrait Pencil, ca. 1948; 2214.BB0293 (Box 140)
  - "Bank On The Democrats" Canning Jar Bank, ca. 1948; 2214.BB0294 (Box 22)
  - Presidential Portrait Plate, Washington through Truman, ca. 1945; 2214.BB0295 (Box 7)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" License Plate Ornament, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0296 (Box 74)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" License Plate Ornament, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0297 (Box 41)
  - Eisenhower "Our Next President" Portrait License Plate Ornament, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0298 (Box 41)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" License Plate Ornament, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0299 (Box 41)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" License Plate Ornament, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0300 (Box 138)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Bumper Sticker Advertisement, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0301 (Box 143)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Portrait Inaugural License Plate, 1953; 2214.BB0302 (Box 41)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Lollipops, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0303 (Box 142)
  - Eisenhower Felt-covered "Ike" Matchbooks, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0304 (Box 227)
  - Eisenhower Convention Score Card Fan, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0305 (Box 138)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Stationery, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0306 (Box 146)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Phonograph Record, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0307 (Box 141)
  - "Eisenhower Speaks to You" Phonograph Record, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0308 (Box 141)
  - Eisenhower "Three Cheers for General Ike" Phonograph Record, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0309 (Box 141)
  - Box of Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Matchbooks, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0310 (Box 227)
  - Stevenson "Adlai In 56" Matchbook, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0311 (Box 227)
  - "Eisenhower-Nixon 1952" Felt-tip Pen, 2214.BB0312 (Box 160)
  - Eisenhower "G.O.P./I Like Ike" Mechanical Pencil, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0313 (Box 160)
  - "Vote For Eisenhower In '52" Pencil, 1952; 2214.BB0314 (Box 160)
  - "Eisenhower For President" Portrait Pencil, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0315 (Box 160)
  - "Eisenhower For President" Portrait Pencil, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0316 (Box 160)
  - Eisenhower "I'm For Ike" Pocket Mirror, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0317 (Box 74)
  - Republican "G.O.P." Matchbook, ca. 1952; 2214.BB0318 (Box 227)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Inaugural Souvenir Parade Viewer, 1953; 2214.BB0319 (Box 148)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Rolled "Inaugural Souvenir" Edition of the Times-Herald, 1953; 2214.BB0320 (Box 165)
  - Eisenhower Inauguration Souvenir Box, 1953; 2214.BB0321 (Box 76)
  - Eisenhower "Give Ike A Republican Congress" Decorative License Plate, 1954; 2214.BB0322 (Box 41)
  - Nixon Color Portrait Electric Sign, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0323 (Box 150)
  - Eisenhower Color Portrait Electric Sign, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0324 (Box 149)
  - Eisenhower Plastic Portrait Plaque, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0325 (Box 145)
  - Republican Convention Metal Tray, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0326 (Box 42)
  - "Eisenhower For President / I Like 'Ike' " Portrait Pencil, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0327 (Box 160)
  - Eisenhower "Write With Ike In '56" Ball-point Pen, 1956; 2214.BB0328 (Box 160)
  - Eisenhower "We Want Ike in '56" Ball-point Pen, 1956; 2214.BB0329 (Box 160)
  - National Democratic Headquarters Pencil, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0330 (Box 160)
  - "Estes Kefauver: The Democrat Who Will WIN" Ball-point Pen, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0331 (Box 160)
  - Eisenhower "Ike in '56" Imitation Quill Pen, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0332 (Box 72)
  - Republican Elephant Paper Fan, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0333 (Box 138)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" / Elephant Soap, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0334 (Box 147)
  - Democratic Donkey Balloon Pipe, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0335 (Box 160)
  - Republican Elephant Balloon Pipe, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0336 (Box 160)
  - Eisenhower-White House Plastic Wallet, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0337 (Box 165)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Glass Ash Tray, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0338 (Box 67)
  - Eisenhower "Clean Up With Ike" Portrait Soap, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0338a (Box 147)
  - Eisenhower "Ike" Republican Elephant Toy, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0339 (Box 69)
  - Stevenson "Adlai" Democratic Donkey Toy, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0340 (Box 69)
  - Eisenhower Portrait Pocket Mirror, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0341 (Box 74)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Elephant Squeaky Toy, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0342 (Box 76)
  - Republican National Convention Elephant Cookie Cutter, 1956; 2214.BB0343 (Box 160)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Elephant Coin Bank, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0344 (Box 76)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon "Vote Republican" Large Campaign Button, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0345 (Box 68)
  - Eisenhower "U.S. For Ike" Large Standing Portrait Button, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0346 (Box 68)
  - Eisenhower "Ike" Cigarette Lighter, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0348 (Box 227)
  - Eisenhower "Ike" Felt Eyeglass Case, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0349 (Box 72)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike For President" Flashing Electric sign, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0350 (Box 148)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Sunglasses, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0351 (Box 165)
  - "Don't Be Static / Vote Democratic" Sunglasses, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0352 (Box 165)
  - Stevenson "U.S.A. Is For Adlai" License Plate Ornament, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0353 (Box 138)
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike" Portrait Ashtray, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0354 (Box 67)
  - Stevenson "All The Way With Adlai" Portrait Ashtray, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0355 (Box 67)
  - Democratic Donkey Soap and Advertisement, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0356 (Box 147)
  - Republican Elephant Soap and Advertising Card, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0357 (Box 147)
  - Stevenson "We're Madly For Adlai" Phonograph Record, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0358 (Box 141)
  - Republican Paper Shopping Bag, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0359 (Box 87)
  - Humphrey Portrait Paper Fan, 1956; 2214.BB0360 (Box 138)
  - Eisenhower-Nixon Matchbooks and Golf Tees, ca. 1955-1956; 2214.BB0361 (Box 227)
  - Eisenhower/Nixon Potholder, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0362 (Box 165)
  - Donkey-Elephant Display Base, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0363 (Box 138)
  - Eisenhower Paper Portrait Fan, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0364 (Box 138)
  - Republican Elephant Mug, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0365 (Box 3)
  - Republican Elephant Plate, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0366 (Box 5)
  - Democratic Donkey Mug, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0367 (Box 3)
  - Democratic Donkey Plate, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0368 (Box 5)
  - "Senator Hubert Humphrey For Vice President" Pen, ca. 1956; 2214.BB0369 (Box 160)
  - Horatio Seymour Painted Portrait Box, ca. 1868; 2214.BB0370 (Box 71)
  - Demonstration Voting Machine, ca. 1928; 2214.BB0371 (Box 52)
  - McKinley-Theodore Roosevelt Portrait Metal Ash Tray, ca. 1900; 2214.BB0372 (Box 42)
  - Hoover-Curtis Portrait Needle Case, 1928; 2214.BB0373 (Box 160)
  - "President and Mrs. John F. Kennedy" Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1961-1963; 2214.BB0374 (Box 12)
  - Eisenhower Ceramic Portrait Head Mug, 1956; 2214.BB0375 (Box 4)
  - Grant Equestrian Portrait Statuette, from Paperweight, 2214.BB0376 (Box 34)
  - McKinley "Patriotism, Protection, & Prosperity" Ceramic Portrait Plate, ca. 1896; 2214.BB0377 (Box 10)
  - Coolidge-Dawes Campaign Thimble, ca. 1924; 2214.BB0379 (Box 160)
  - "Let's Sew It Up For A Republican Victory" Campaign Thimble, 2214.BB0380 (Box 160)
  - Republican Elephant Ceramic Liquor Bottle, 1960; 2214.BB0381 (Box 24)
  - Democratic Donkey Ceramic Liquor Bottle, 1960; 2214.BB0382 (Box 24)
  - Willkie Life-Size Standing Cutout Portrait, ca. 1940; 2214.BB0383 (Box TBD)
  - Obama toilet paper, Undated; 2214.BB0384 (Box 76)
- Series III. Books
  Books: Susan Douglas donated a small quantity of books to Cornell, most of which are secondary reference sources on American politics. Items in the "Books" category will not be digitized by the Political Americana Project.
  - A Synchronic Chart and Statistical Tables of United States History, 1911; 2214.BK0001 (Box TBD)
  - Mirror of Modern Democracy: A History of the Democratic Party, From its Organization in 1825 to its Last Great Achievement, the Rebellion of 1861, 1864; 2214.BK0002 (Box TBD)
  - The National Conventions and Platforms of All Political Parties: 1789 to 1900, 2214.BK0003 (Box TBD)
  - Rise and Fall of Political Parties in the United States, 1884; 2214.BK0004 (Box TBD)
  - A Dictionary of American Politics, Comprising Accounts of Political Parties, Measures and Men, Etc., 1892; 2214.BK0005 (Box TBD)
  - Dictionary of American Politics, 1955; 2214.BK0006 (Box TBD)
  - A Book About American Politics, 1952; 2214.BK0007 (Box TBD)
  - They Also Ran: The Story of the Men Who were Defeated for the Presidency, 1954; 2214.BK0008 (Box TBD)
  - The President's Daughter, 1927; 2214.BK0009 (Box TBD)
  - Candidates 1960: Behind the Headlines in the Presidential Race, 1959; 2214.BK0010 (Box TBD)
  - American Parties and Elections, 1927; 2214.BK0011 (Box TBD)
  - The Lunatic Fringe, 1957; 2214.BK0012 (Box TBD)
  - The Great Game of Politics, 1928; 2214.BK0013 (Box TBD)
- Series IV. Broadsides
  Broadsides: This series contains an assortment of promotional, declaratory, and advertising items. Most of these items are made of paper, advertised particular events or politically-related products, and were intended to have a very short use-life. Mrs. Douglas also included some of the collection's bumper stickers in this category.
  - Taylor, ca. 1848; 2214.BR0001 (Box TBD)
  - Let's Clean House with Ike and Dick, ca. 1952; 2214.BR0002 (Box 94)
  - Let's Clean House with Ike and Dick, ca. 1952; 2214.BR0003 (Box TBD)
  - Jersey Welcomes Eisenhower, ca. 1952; 2214.BR0004 (Box TBD)
  - Turn Gloom to Boom with Douglas, ca. 1948; 2214.BR0005 (Box 88)
  - The Silver Dollar: Read the Record, ca. 1892; 2214.BR0006 (Box TBD)
  - Forward with Stevenson, ca. 1952; 2214.BR0008 (Box 91)
  - "Let's Clean House with Ike and Dick" Bumper Sticker, ca. 1952; 2214.BR0009 (Box 138)
  - Eisenhower, Nixon, and Smith Bumper Sticker, ca. 1952; 2214.BR0010 (Box 141)
  - Eisenhower for President Bumper Sticker, ca. 1952; 2214.BR0011 (Box 141)
  - Going Up Salt River on the Republican Excursion, ca. 1932; 2214.BR0012 (Box 91)
  - The Erie Railroad will run Special Trains to the State Fair at Elmira, 1884; 2214.BR0013 (Box 91)
  - The Bird that Crows for Cleveland!, 1892; 2214.BR0014 (Box 91)
  - The Eisenhower Prayer, 1953; 2214.BR0015 (Box 94)
  - Funeral Ceremonies of William Henry Harrison, 1841; 2214.BR0016 (Box 92)
  - Above the Storm, 1948; 2214.BR0017 (Box 91)
  - See Willkie Today, ca. 1940; 2214.BR0018 (Box TBD)
  - Boomerang!! Truman's Big Lie Bites Him Back, ca. 1952; 2214.BR0019 (Box 92)
  - Illinois Primary Election Results, ca. 1948; 2214.BR0021 (Box 92)
  - General Scott Denounced!, ca. 1852; 2214.BR0022 (Box 92)
  - AFL Building Trades President Endorses Eisenhower, 1952; 2214.BR0023 (Box 94)
  - A Wide-Open Convention can turn this into a Wide-Open Campaign, ca. 1948; 2214.BR0024 (Box 92)
  - Win With Douglas, ca. 1948; 2214.BR0025 (Box 92)
  - Stevenson Draft Swells, ca. 1952; 2214.BR0026 (Box TBD)
  - Democratic National Convention!, ca. 1868; 2214.BR0027 (Box 92)
  - The Republican Record, ca. 1890; 2214.BR0028 (Box 92)
  - To Whom it may Concern, ca. 1948; 2214.BR0029 (Box 92)
  - Stassen's Platform, ca. 1952; 2214.BR0030 (Box 92)
  - Big Ike Rally!, ca. 1952; 2214.BR0031 (Box 92)
  - His Future is in Your Hands!, 1952; 2214.BR0032 (Box 92)
  - What Makes a Good Man Bad?, ca. 1952; 2214.BR0033 (Box 94)
  - The Man of the Hour, ca. 1948; 2214.BR0034 (Box 94)